

CONTACT

- **Q** Sweden Malmö
- Moussa.Lakki@hotmail.com
- (in) <u>linkedin.com/in/moussaellakki</u>
- +46739612818
- GitHub
- <u> Portfolio</u>

SKILLS

- Communication
- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Swift
- SwiftUI
- UIKit
- MVVM
- MVC
- Cocoapods
- Kotlin
- Java
- C#
- Firebase
- Git & Github
- API Networking
- UI/UX Design
- Figma

LANGUAGES

- Swedish Fluent
- English Proficient
- Arabic Native

MOUSSA EL LAKKI iOS Developer

Skilled mobile application developer specializing in iOS. I started my career by learning programming at Folkuniversitetet in 2019. Since I started learning mobile development. I have developed and released three apps to the App Store and Google Play. My portfolio showcases my work.

I am a quick learner and also a team player who loves writing code that is easy to read and manage. I also have good problem-solving skills, troubleshooting, and time management abilities.

EDUCATION

MALMÖ YRKESHÖGSKOLA

2021 - 2022 Programmerare IPhone & Android

KOMVUX

2020 - 2021 Programming 2

Hermods

2019 - 2020 Programming 1

FOLKUNIVERSITETET

2019 - 2020 Programming for beginners

MALMÖ FOLKHÖGSKOLA

2007 - 2010 High school

EXPERIENCE

MALMÖ YRKESHÖGSKOLA

2021 - 2022 Projects

Developed and released three mobile apps on the App Store and Google Play.

TETRA PAK AB

2016 - 2019 Functional tester

I was working as a functional and technical tester, and mainly worked with assembling and testing hardware to ensure that it was functioning correctly.

GFAB GLASTEAM AB

2010-2016 Machine Operator

Cut custom glass products using computer-controlled cutting and shaping machinery.

Glass Design

2004 - 2007 Business Founder/Owner

I ran a small business selling and fabricating custom glass products using in-house machinery.

El Ghoul Co.

2000 - 2004 Machine Operator

Operated cutting/shaping machines via PC panel to cut and shape glass to specific dimensions."